[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was actress Sheree Elizabeth Zampino married to from 1992 to 1995?", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Terrell Fletcher", "James Avery", "Alfonso Ribeiro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which commercial building can also store data?", "correct_answer": "Warehouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Super market", "Store", "Shop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed with curly hair appeared as a natural mutation in the United States.", "correct_answer": "LaPerm", "incorrect_answers": ["Selkirk Rex", "Kurilian Bobtail", "American Curl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Muscles push and pull-- thats how you can wriggle your fingers back and forth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are the orbits in which the electrons of the atom reside called?", "correct_answer": "Electron shells", "incorrect_answers": ["Electron orbits", "Electron paths", "Electron circles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This medical condition is characterized by subsequent decay of body tissues, caused by infection or thrombosis or lack of blood flow.", "correct_answer": "Gangrene", "incorrect_answers": ["Scleroderma", "Tinea", "Impetigo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Billy Jack Goes to Washington released?", "correct_answer": "1977", "incorrect_answers": ["1979", "1976", "1978"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these most accurately describes the medical term, necrosis?", "correct_answer": "Death of living tissue", "incorrect_answers": ["Irregular heartbeat", "Decrease in white blood cells", "Liver damage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which musical artist/band was not associated with the Back to the Future movies?", "correct_answer": "Bon Jovi", "incorrect_answers": ["Huey Lewis", "ZZ Top", "Van Halen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Academy Award-winning actress portrayed Norma Rae Webster in the 1979 movie Norma Rae.", "correct_answer": "Sally Field", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Jane Fonda", "Diane Keaton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of the following two movies did Dustin Hoffman win Oscars?", "correct_answer": "Kramer vs. Kramer and Rain Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Midnight Cowboy and Lenny", "Wag the Dog and Kramer vs. Kramer", "Tootsie and The Graduate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did President Franklin Roosevelt give the approval for dropping the first atom bomb on Japan?", "correct_answer": "He never did", "incorrect_answers": ["1946", "1945", "1944"]}]